>> Brian Holt: 因此，我们将返回 " React" ，不再使用工具。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So we're going back to
React, away from tooling for a while.
所以我要让我的服务器在后台运行
So I'm just gonna leave my server
running in the background here.
> > Brian Holt: 是的，然后我们继续。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Yeah, and
then we'll keep going.
到目前为止我一直在给你展示
So far, I've been showing you
how to write React without
任何真正的示爱或者任何类似的东西都是在兜帽下面
any really transpilation or anything like
that just raw React underneath the hood.
但我想让你看看这个叫 JSX的功能
But I wanna show you how to
use this feature called JSX,
因为我们现在使用包裹可以使用 JSX
because we're using parcel
now we can use JSX,
而我们之前不可能因为包裹没有在我们的代码上运行
whereas we could not before because
parcel was not running on our code.
包裹在用一个叫巴贝尔的项目进行变换
And parcel do transformations
using a project called Babel,
是个很酷的项目
which is a really cool project.
这只是建在一个包裹里好吗
And that's just built into parcel, okay?
所以我们来了，我们还是先去做 pet.js 吧。
So here we have,
let's actually go do pet.js first.
>> Brian Holt: 好的，现在你在看这个项目，你可以看到
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, so you're looking at
this project right now, and you can see
这会用 h1 和两个 h2的内部创建一个 div ，对吧 ?
that this is gonna create a div with
an h1 and two h2's inside of it, right?
所以我们在用 JavaScript 来模仿标记，对吧 ?
So we're writing JavaScript
to mimic markup, right?
所以当你考虑好的时候大脑内部
So inside of your brain when
you're thinking about okay, well,
我要在里面有一个我要有一个 h1 和 h2的 div 。
I need to have a div inside of
that I need to have an h1 and h2.
你得想想你想要的 HTML
You have to think about
the HTML that you want and
那就得把你大脑里的那个转化为能做的 JavaScript ，对吧 ?
then have to translate that in your brain
to JavaScript that React can do, right?
如果我们能把我们想要的 HTML 写得更好
Wouldn't it be nice if we could just write
the HTML that we wanted in the first place
而不是在我们的大脑里有那个翻译层吗
rather than having to have that
translation layer in our brain?
这就是 JSX 的情况，就像所有 JSX 都一样。
Well, that's what JSX is and
like that is all JSX is.
这不是别的事
It's not anything else,
除了我刚才告诉你的事情外还有其他的特点
there's not additional features
beyond just what I just told you.
>> Brian Holt: 所以我就像这样评论这个。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So I'll comment this
out for just a second just like this.
我想让你说回来，然后我想你这样写，好吗 ?
And I want you to say return, and then I
want you to write div like this, okay?
然后我想让你把一个 h1 放在那个 h1 里面
And then inside of that div I want you
to put an h1 and then inside of that h1,
我要你用花括号括起来
I want you to put curly braces
like that and put name.
然后一个 h2，而不是花在里面的背带，我们可以做动物。
Then an h2, and instead of curly braces
inside of that, we could do animal.
在另一个 h2中
And inside of another h2,
可能猜中了吧
probably guessed breed, yeah?
>> 扬声器 2: 在 JSX 中是否有写快捷方式 ?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Are there any Emmit
shortcuts for writing in JSX?
>> Brian Holt: 有，当然有。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: There are, yeah, for sure.
我是否有，嗯， > > Brian Holt: 我很确定
Do I have it, yeah, so
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: I'm pretty sure
你现在要做的就是， >> Brian Holt: 让我们试试吧。
the way you have to do that right now is,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Let's just try it.
>> Brian Holt: 是，如果我将此更改为 .jsx，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Yeah, so
if I change this to be .jsx,
就能把它从盒子里取出来
it would just work out of the box.
有一种可以为 JS 文件启用的方法，我忘了怎么做。
There's a way to enable it for
JS files, and I forgot how to do it.
但让我们先谈一下为什么我不改变一切
But so let's just talk for a second about
why I'm not changing everything to be
.jsx，我不这么做的真正原因是因为 React
.jsx, the real reason I'm not doing that
in teaching that too is because the React
核心小组说他们认为没必要这样我就不这么做了
core team said that they don't think it's
necessary, so I don't do it and that's it.
但如果你做的改变是 .jsx ，你会得到一些免费的东西。
But if you do changes it be .jsx you'll
get some of that stuff for free.
>> 扬声器 3: 其他方法只是更改类型
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: The other way
is just to change the type in
VS 到 JavaScript 的 JavaScript 代码。
VS Code to JavaScript React
from JavaScript.
所以在底部上面写着 JavaScript
So on the bottom there
it's says JavaScript,
如果您将其更改为 JavaScript React。
if you change it to JavaScript React.
>> Brian Holt: 这也会起作用。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: That'll work as well.
>> 演讲者 3: 这也会起作用。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: That'll work as well.
>> Brian Holt: 现在我可以这样做了。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
now I can do h2 like that.
>> Brian Holt: 有一种方法可以始终配置这些 .js 文件
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: There's a way to
configure those .js files always
也有这方面的资料
have that available as well.
但我相信如果你谷歌它，它会成为最大的栈溢出问题。
But I'm sure if you Google it,
it'll be the top stack overflow question.
所以我们现在把这个翻译成
So we've now translated this
这些都是等同的，对吧 ?
to this and
these are equivalent right now, right?
我个人告诉你，我认为这更容易阅读，对吧 ?
I will personally tell you that I think
this is far more readable, right?
没有代码，密度不高，没有对象和引号，
There's less code, it's less dense,
there's not objects and quotes and
就像这样
things like that.
但当雷法首次启动时，这是一个巨大的障碍
But when React was first starting out,
this was a big barrier for
有很多人
a lot of people.
这是个大障碍因为我们花了很长时间从我们的
It was a big barrier because we took
a long time getting JavaScript out of our
HTML，现在我们把 HTML 放到我们的 JavaScript 里，对吧 ?
HTML, and now we're putting HTML
into our JavaScript, right?
而这种感觉是错误的。
And that just feels wrong.
但我要告诉你这更好，因为它不一样。
But I'll tell you that this is
better because it's not the same.
把 JavaScript 放到你的 HTML 里是个糟糕的想法
Putting JavaScript inside of your HTML was
a terrible idea, and whoever started doing
他们把我们安排了五年如果我们完全诚实对吗
that, they set us back like five years,
if we're being totally honest, right?
但是，我们只是在编写我们真正想要的 HTML 代码。
But whereas this, we're just writing the
HTML that we actually want in the code.
现在我想让你知道这只小的 div 标记
And now I want you to know
that this little div tag here,
都被翻译成这样了
literally gets translated to this.
如果你看看错位的输出，对吧 ?
If you go look at the transpiled output,
right?
所以在这一经历穿过了 Babble之后
So after this gets ran through Babble,
这里的一切都被翻译成 React.create.ElementCalls ，对吧 ?
everything here is just being translated
into React.create.ElementCalls, right?
所以这里没有什么神秘的
So there's no mystery here.
它不做任何黑魔法或优化之类的事情。
It's not doing any sort of black magic or
optimization or anything like that.
从字面上来说，把它放进密码里的是这个，不是这个，这个。
Literally what gets put it in
the code is this,oops not that, this.
这就是为什么我让你先写这些东西让你明白
That's why I have you write all this stuff
first so you understand that this is all
只是 React.createElementCalls ，这里没有任何 amiss 。
just React.createElementCalls,
and there's nothing amiss here.
有道理吗
Does that make sense?
>> Brian Holt: 我向您保证， JSX 中没有其他内容，这是真的。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And I promise you, there's
nothing else in JSX, this is really it.
还有谁有问题吗
Anyone else have any questions, yeah?
>> 扬声器 4: 我注意到，有时如果您
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: I have noticed
that sometimes if you
尝试在您的返回中进行多个 div 。
try to make multiple
divs in your return and
你的 JSX 就会黄了你得有办法把它包起来
your JSX it yells at you and
you need to have something to wrap it all.
>> Brian Holt: 对。 >> 演讲者 4: 有具体原因吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Yep.
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Is there specific reason?
我是说我只知道只回来一件事
I mean, I understand the idea
of returning only one thing but.
>> Brian Holt: 我的意思是这样，对吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: I mean that's precisely it,
right?
所以如果我说的话， >> Brian Holt: 如果我把这个放在这里，对吧 ?
So if I put like,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: If I put this here, right?
它会说我不知道相邻的 JSX
It's gonna say,
I don't know what to, adjacent JSX
元素必须包装在外层标签中，谢谢， ESLint 为我们捕捉到它，对吗 ?
elements must be wrapped in enclosing tag,
thanks, ESLint caught it for us, right?
所以，让我们先谈这个问题。
So let's talk about this for a second.
如果我有这个，这会被翻译成什么呢 ?
What does this get translated
to if I have this?
如果我没说过的话
Well, if I uncommented this
it would be like having,
>> Brian Holt: React.createElement 或
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: React.createElement or
contextElement，停止每个 h1 右边的元素，如那样。
contextElement, stop it element
each h1 right, something like that.
> > Brian Holt: 这没有任何意义，因为你不能归还两个东西，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And this doesn't make any
sense because you can't return two things,
对吧 ?
right?
我不能说退货 2，逗号 5，对吧 ?
I can't say return 2, comma 5, right?
JavaScript 没有此能力，
JavaScript does not have this ability,
某些其他语言具有多个返回，但不具有 JavaScript。
some other languages have multiple
returns, but not JavaScript.
所以这就是 React 要求你回去的原因
So that's why React requires you to return
一个顶级的东西，因为这个是 JavaScript 可以做的。
one top level thing because
that's what JavaScript can do.
现在有一种方法可以做到这一点我们稍后会被称为
Now there is a way to accomplish this
which we'll get to later which are called
片段，但是您返回一个包含两个内容的顶级片段，
fragments, but you return one top-level
fragment which encapsulates two things,
有道理 > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 好的，
does that make sense
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: All right,
我们走吧
let's get rid of that.
所以如果你觉得这种感觉很奇怪，很多人还是会觉得奇怪的，
So if this still feels weird to you,
a lot of people will still feel weird to,
我邀请你用这个完成课程
I would invite you to just
finish the course with this.
我要告诉你只有一两个主要的公司
I will tell you that there's only one or
two major holdouts of companies that
没有使用 JSX ，现在我知道的两个大的都使用 JSX，对吧 ?
didn't use JSX and now both of the big
ones that I know of now use JSX, right?
就是 React 社区中的每个人都是 JSX 和其他人
It's just everyone in the React community
is JSX and people like it enough that
甚至 Vue 社区也有人使用 JSX ，对吧 ?
even the Vue community some of
them use JSX as well, right?
所以这是一个非常好的模式。
So it's it's a pretty good pattern.